<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<root>
	<data>
		<!--************** XML DATA ************** -->
		<main>
			<xslPath>E:\sas-master\src\main\webapp\xsl\</xslPath>
			<imgPath>E:\sas-master\src\main\webapp\support\img\</imgPath>

			<Company_Logo>sosheader.jpg</Company_Logo>
			<range>range.jpg</range>
			<wallpaper>wallpaper.jpg</wallpaper>
			<user>abc</user>
			<score>100%</score>
			<desc11> You are well progressed in the design and maturity </desc11>
			<desc12> of your risk mitigation program for globally mobile </desc12>
			<desc13> employees. Minor improvements and ongoing monitoring
			</desc13>
			<desc14> is appropriate by the responsible cross- functional team.
			</desc14>
			<desc21>Integrated Travel Risk Mitigation, a Duty of Care
				Plan-Do-Check approach
			</desc21>
			<desc22>International SOS commissioned the first ever Duty of Care
				whitepaper. This reviews employers Duty of Care responsibilities and
				offers guidelines for the development of appropriate risk management
				strategies.
			</desc22>
			<desc23>Following this sector first, our clients requested more
				research, tools and advice. Resulting in the commission of our Duty
				of Care and Travel Risk Management Global Benchmarking Study the
				first comprehensive and
				authoritative research publication on the
				topic.
			</desc23>
			<desc24>The paper outlines a framework for organisations to ensure
				they are adequately meeting their Duty of Care obligations. The
				framework follows the 'plan-do-check' approach.
			</desc24>
			<desc25>For more information</desc25>
			<desc31> Need assistance with any of your responses or
				recommendations?
			</desc31>
			<desc32>Contact International SOS - inquiries@internationalsos.com|
			</desc32>
			<desc33>The recommendations, suggested actions and broad maturity
				measure are for guidance purposes only and do not constitute formal
				advice. Please
			</desc33>
			<desc34>contact International SOS for customised analysis and
				recommendations specific to your organisation
			</desc34>
			<riskMitigation>
				<strategy>
					<title>Plan</title>
					<question>
						<title>Q1</title>
						<value>Can you locate all your current travellers?
						</value>
						<action>
							this is description for this question: Can you locate all
							your current
							travellers?
						</action>
					</question>
					<question>
						<title>Q2</title>
						<value>Do you access the risks to your employees in those
							locations?
						</value>
						<action>
							this is description for this question: Do you access the
							risks to your employees in those locations?
						</action>
					</question>
					<question>
						<title>Q3</title>
						<value>Do you monitor the type and quantity of incidents your
							employees have been involved in over the last 2-3 years?
						</value>
						<action>
							this is description for this question: Do you monitor the
							type and quantity of incidents your employees have been involved
							in over the last 2-3 years?
						</action>
					</question>
					<question>
						<title>Q4</title>
						<value>Does your company understand its Duty of Care obligations?
						</value>
						<action>
							this is description for this question: Does your company
							understand its Duty of Care obligations?
						</action>
					</question>
					<question>
						<title>Q5</title>
						<value>Do your policies cover the health, safety and security of
							employees abroad?
						</value>
						<action>
							this is description for this question: Do your policies
							cover the health, safety and security of employees abroad?
						</action>
					</question>
					<question>
						<title>Q6</title>
						<value>Do you know who is responsible for Travel Risk Management
							in
							your organisation?
						</value>
						<action>
							this is description for this question: Do you know who is
							responsible for Travel Risk Management in your organisation?
						</action>
					</question>
					<question>
						<title>Q7</title>
						<value>Do you know how to integrate the components of Travel Risk
							Management into your risk management system?
						</value>
						<action>
							this is description for this question: Do you know how to
							integrate the components of Travel Risk Management into your risk
							management system?
						</action>
					</question>
				</strategy>
				<strategy>
					<title>Do</title>
					<question>
						<title>Q1</title>
						<value>Do you have a travel approval process that includes travel
							risk assessments?
						</value>
						<action>
							this is description for this question: Do you have a travel
							approval process that includes travel risk assessments?
						</action>
					</question>
					<question>
						<title>Q2</title>
						<value>Do your employees have access to relevant information &amp;
							advice to support them when making these risk assessments?
						</value>
						<action>
							this is description for this question: Do your employees
							have access to relevant information &amp; advice to support them
							when
							making these risk assessments?
						</action>
					</question>
					<question>
						<title>Q3</title>
						<value>Do you have plans in place if things go wrong?
						</value>
						<action>
							this is description for this question: Do you have plans in
							place if things go wrong?
						</action>
					</question>
					<question>
						<title>Q4</title>
						<value>Do you check the safety and security of hotels and
							accommodation?
						</value>
						<action>
							this is description for this question: Do you check the
							safety and security of hotels and accommodation?
						</action>
					</question>
					<question>
						<title>Q5</title>
						<value>Do you know how many RTA's(Road Traffic Accidents) your
							company has experienced in the last 3 years?
						</value>
						<action>
							this is description for this question: Do you know how many
							RTA's(Road Traffic Accidents) your company has experienced in the
							last 3 years?
						</action>
					</question>
					<question>
						<title>Q6</title>
						<value>Do you assess the fitness for travel for expatriate or
							travelling staff?
						</value>
						<action>
							this is description for this question:Do you assess the
							fitness for travel for expatriate or travelling staff?
						</action>
					</question>
					<question>
						<title>Q7</title>
						<value>Do you have a program to help employees understand and
							manage their existing health issues whist away?
						</value>
						<action>
							this is description for this question: Do you have a
							program to help employees understand and manage their existing
							health issues whist away?
						</action>
					</question>
					<question>
						<title>Q8</title>
						<value>Are your employees aware of your Travel Risk Mitigation
							plans and their responsibilities?
						</value>
						<action>
							this is description for this question: Are your employees
							aware of your Travel Risk Mitigation plans and their
							responsibilities?
						</action>
					</question>
					<question>
						<title>Q9</title>
						<value>Do your employees receive training about the risks at the
							destinations they are travelling to?
						</value>
						<action>
							this is description for this question: Do your employees
							receive training about the risks at the destinations they are
							travelling to?
						</action>
					</question>
					<question>
						<title>Q10</title>
						<value>Do your managers understand their responsibilities when
							approving travel?
						</value>
						<action>
							this is description for this question: Do your managers
							understand their responsibilities when approving travel?
						</action>
					</question>
					<question>
						<title>Q11</title>
						<value>Do you have a system in place to inform your people of a
							situation that may impact them?
						</value>
						<action>
							this is description for this question: Do you have a system
							in place to inform your people of a situation that may impact
							them?
						</action>
					</question>
					<question>
						<title>Q12</title>
						<value>Do you have a system in place to quickly account for
							employees in an emergency?
						</value>
						<action>
							this is description for this question: Do you have a system
							in place to quickly account for employees in an emergency?
						</action>
					</question>
					<question>
						<title>Q13</title>
						<value>Do your employees have access to advice and support 24/7?
						</value>
						<action>
							this is description for this question: Do your employees
							have access to advice and support 24/7?
						</action>
					</question>
					<question>
						<title>Q14</title>
						<value>Do you have measures in place to check the health of
							employees returning to work?
						</value>
						<action>
							this is description for this question: Do you have measures
							in place to check the health of employees returning to work?
						</action>
					</question>
				</strategy>
				<strategy>
					<title>Check</title>
					<question>
						<title>Q1</title>
						<value>Are your plans and procedures tested for effectiveness?
						</value>
						<action>
							this is description for this question: Are your plans and
							procedures tested for effectiveness?
						</action>
					</question>
					<question>
						<title>Q2</title>
						<value>Do you have a system in place to ensure compliance with
							your
							policies and procedures?
						</value>
						<action>
							this is description for this question: Do you have a system
							in place to ensure compliance with your policies and procedures?
						</action>
					</question>
				</strategy>
			</riskMitigation>
		</main>
	</data>
</root>
